[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110816pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBG", "VBZ", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 14, "question": "Is it going to come to praying again?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "it", "going", "to", "come", "to", "praying", "again", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "TO", "VB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 15, "answer": "Well, praying does help.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "praying", "does", "help", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110816pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "CD", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 29, "question": "What was the most striking part of it from your point of view?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "the", "most", "striking", "part", "of", "it", "from", "your", "point", "of", "view", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "DT", "JJS", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 30, "answer": "At one point, we started talking about the tenth anniversary of 9/11.", "answer_tokens": ["At", "one", "point", ",", "we", "started", "talking", "about", "the", "tenth", "anniversary", "of", "9/11", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110816pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "RBR", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 44, "question": "How had he changed physically and in himself and his demeanor to you?", "question_tokens": ["How", "had", "he", "changed", "physically", "and", "in", "himself", "and", "his", "demeanor", "to", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "CC", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 45, "answer": "He's got a lot more gray hair.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "'s", "got", "a", "lot", "more", "gray", "hair", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110816pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 83, "question": "Has the election proper started now, do you think?", "question_tokens": ["Has", "the", "election", "proper", "started", "now", ",", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "VBD", "RB", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 84, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110816pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "VBZ", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 102, "question": "What's your overview of what the president is up to and where he stands?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "your", "overview", "of", "what", "the", "president", "is", "up", "to", "and", "where", "he", "stands", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "WP", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "TO", "CC", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 103, "answer": "Well, I mean, my overview is that president is seeing the impact of the results that he's had.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "mean", ",", "my", "overview", "is", "that", "president", "is", "seeing", "the", "impact", "of", "the", "results", "that", "he", "'s", "had", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110816pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 117, "question": "Would you agree with that?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "you", "agree", "with", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 118, "answer": "I don't know yet.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", "yet", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110816pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 133, "question": "Are you feeling more inclined to run now or less inclined?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "feeling", "more", "inclined", "to", "run", "now", "or", "less", "inclined", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "JJR", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "RB", "CC", "JJR", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 134, "answer": "I don't think I've changed my thinking about it very much.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "think", "I", "'ve", "changed", "my", "thinking", "about", "it", "very", "much", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["China"]}, "docId": "110816pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "WDT", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 151, "question": "What is wrong with that?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "wrong", "with", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 152, "answer": "Well, because the only way you're going to increase confidence in the American economy which China is worried about and the rest of the world is to stop us from spending money.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "because", "the", "only", "way", "you", "'re", "going", "to", "increase", "confidence", "in", "the", "American", "economy", "which", "China", "is", "worried", "about", "and", "the", "rest", "of", "the", "world", "is", "to", "stop", "us", "from", "spending", "money", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110816pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 168, "question": "Let me ask you -- if you don't run, Rudy, which of the candidates at the moment is the one that you would feel most comfortable being the nominee for the Republicans?", "question_tokens": ["Let", "me", "ask", "you", "--", "if", "you", "do", "n't", "run", ",", "Rudy", ",", "which", "of", "the", "candidates", "at", "the", "moment", "is", "the", "one", "that", "you", "would", "feel", "most", "comfortable", "being", "the", "nominee", "for", "the", "Republicans", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", ":", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", ",", "NNP", ",", "WDT", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "CD", "WDT", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RBS", "JJ", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNPS", "."], "aSentId": 169, "answer": "I haven't really focused in on it.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "have", "n't", "really", "focused", "in", "on", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Rudy"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110816pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 177, "question": "Is it conceivable, do you think, that a Tea Party candidate like a Michele Bachmann could end up being the nominee?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "it", "conceivable", ",", "do", "you", "think", ",", "that", "a", "Tea", "Party", "candidate", "like", "a", "Michele", "Bachmann", "could", "end", "up", "being", "the", "nominee", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "JJ", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "MD", "VB", "RP", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 178, "answer": "Sure is.", "answer_tokens": ["Sure", "is", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Michele Bachmann"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["September"]}, "docId": "110816pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", ",", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJS", "."], "qSentId": 189, "question": "Funny, Rudy, what's the latest you could leave it personally to make a decision as to whether or not you're going to run?", "question_tokens": ["Funny", ",", "Rudy", ",", "what", "'s", "the", "latest", "you", "could", "leave", "it", "personally", "to", "make", "a", "decision", "as", "to", "whether", "or", "not", "you", "'re", "going", "to", "run", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJS", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "TO", "IN", "CC", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 190, "answer": "End of September, I'd say, would be the latest.", "answer_tokens": ["End", "of", "September", ",", "I", "'d", "say", ",", "would", "be", "the", "latest", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Rudy"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Wolf Blitzer"]}, "docId": "110816pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "RP", "."], "qSentId": 203, "question": "How did he seem to you?", "question_tokens": ["How", "did", "he", "seem", "to", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 204, "answer": "I think, you know, like we see with Wolf Blitzer today, the president is pumped up.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", ",", "you", "know", ",", "like", "we", "see", "with", "Wolf", "Blitzer", "today", ",", "the", "president", "is", "pumped", "up", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110816pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 211, "question": "If you were his teacher and you were doing a school report after three years, good marks and where could he be better?", "question_tokens": ["If", "you", "were", "his", "teacher", "and", "you", "were", "doing", "a", "school", "report", "after", "three", "years", ",", "good", "marks", "and", "where", "could", "he", "be", "better", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "CD", "NNS", ",", "JJ", "NNS", "CC", "WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "JJR", "."], "aSentId": 212, "answer": "I think he has great marks.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "he", "has", "great", "marks", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Warren Buffett"]}, "docId": "110816pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 221, "question": "So, you agree with Warren Buffett?", "question_tokens": ["So", ",", "you", "agree", "with", "Warren", "Buffett", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 222, "answer": "I agree with Warren Buffett.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "agree", "with", "Warren", "Buffett", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Warren Buffett"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110816pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 224, "question": "The rich should get pay more?", "question_tokens": ["The", "rich", "should", "get", "pay", "more", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "MD", "VB", "NN", "JJR", "."], "aSentId": 225, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110816pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 232, "question": "Since John Kennedy said ask not what your country can do for you, what you're going to do for your country?", "question_tokens": ["Since", "John", "Kennedy", "said", "ask", "not", "what", "your", "country", "can", "do", "for", "you", ",", "what", "you", "'re", "going", "to", "do", "for", "your", "country", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "NN", "RB", "WP", "PRP$", "NN", "MD", "VB", "IN", "PRP", ",", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 233, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["John Kennedy"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110816pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBN", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 241, "question": "So he's got his work cut out, hasn't he?", "question_tokens": ["So", "he", "'s", "got", "his", "work", "cut", "out", ",", "has", "n't", "he", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "RP", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 242, "answer": "Well, I think he's already, you know, made spectacular gains.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "he", "'s", "already", ",", "you", "know", ",", "made", "spectacular", "gains", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110816pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "JJ", "JJR", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 271, "question": "And how do you fix it with jobs, do you think?", "question_tokens": ["And", "how", "do", "you", "fix", "it", "with", "jobs", ",", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "NNS", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 272, "answer": "I think the president, has much better ways than me as a producer.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "the", "president", ",", "has", "much", "better", "ways", "than", "me", "as", "a", "producer", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Google"]}, "docId": "110816pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 281, "question": "You are hiring more staff?", "question_tokens": ["You", "are", "hiring", "more", "staff", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "JJR", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 282, "answer": "Apple, Google -- I am.", "answer_tokens": ["Apple", ",", "Google", "--", "I", "am", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110816pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 296, "question": "Is this about Michelle Obama, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "this", "about", "Michelle", "Obama", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "DT", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 297, "answer": "She's tall.", "answer_tokens": ["She", "'s", "tall", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Michelle Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Sandra", "Ryan"]}, "docId": "110816pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", ",", "``", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", ",", "''", "PRP", "VBD", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 315, "question": "But the crucial battle theme, you're a competitive man, is you're very near to beating Sandra Bullock and Ryan Reynolds in the number of people who viewed this, right?", "question_tokens": ["But", "the", "crucial", "battle", "theme", ",", "you", "'re", "a", "competitive", "man", ",", "is", "you", "'re", "very", "near", "to", "beating", "Sandra", "Bullock", "and", "Ryan", "Reynolds", "in", "the", "number", "of", "people", "who", "viewed", "this", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "TO", "NN", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "WP", "VBN", "DT", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 316, "answer": "The first week that Sandra and Ryan did the proposal, \"Funny or Die,\" they did 600,000.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "first", "week", "that", "Sandra", "and", "Ryan", "did", "the", "proposal", ",", "``", "Funny", "or", "Die", ",", "''", "they", "did", "600,000", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Sandra Bullock", "Ryan Reynolds"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110816pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 373, "question": "It's a negative thing, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["It", "'s", "a", "negative", "thing", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 374, "answer": "I don't find it negative at all.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "find", "it", "negative", "at", "all", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110816pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 388, "question": "I do really?", "question_tokens": ["I", "do", "really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 389, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110816pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 390, "question": "Do I really anger you?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "I", "really", "anger", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "JJR", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 391, "answer": "You do.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "do", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110816pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 408, "question": "How did we get here?", "question_tokens": ["How", "did", "we", "get", "here", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 409, "answer": "Let me ask you.", "answer_tokens": ["Let", "me", "ask", "you", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110816pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "VBG", ",", "DT", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 410, "question": "How did we get here?", "question_tokens": ["How", "did", "we", "get", "here", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 411, "answer": "I believe in this superior being, a God.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "believe", "in", "this", "superior", "being", ",", "a", "God", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110816pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "JJR", "TO", "NN", ":", "VBG", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 423, "question": "Because I never hear an atheist give me any answers to how did we get here and what happens at the end of our lives?", "question_tokens": ["Because", "I", "never", "hear", "an", "atheist", "give", "me", "any", "answers", "to", "how", "did", "we", "get", "here", "and", "what", "happens", "at", "the", "end", "of", "our", "lives", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "VBP", "PRP", "DT", "NNS", "TO", "WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "CC", "WP", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 424, "answer": "But answer to something -- saying we can't understand it is not an answer.", "answer_tokens": ["But", "answer", "to", "something", "--", "saying", "we", "ca", "n't", "understand", "it", "is", "not", "an", "answer", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110816pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 426, "question": "How do you think we got here?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "think", "we", "got", "here", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 427, "answer": "I don't know.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110816pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 428, "question": "What do you think happens when whether you die?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "happens", "when", "whether", "you", "die", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "NNS", "WRB", "IN", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 429, "answer": "Well, nothing.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "nothing", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["1890"]}, "docId": "110816pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 438, "question": "What do you think happens to you?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "happens", "to", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "NNS", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 439, "answer": "How scared of you are of 1890.", "answer_tokens": ["How", "scared", "of", "you", "are", "of", "1890", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110816pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CD", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 441, "question": "1890?", "question_tokens": ["1890", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CD", "."], "aSentId": 442, "answer": "1890, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["1890", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110816pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 444, "question": "You weren't alive then, right?", "question_tokens": ["You", "were", "n't", "alive", "then", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "RB", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 445, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110816pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 448, "question": "Is that a horror to you?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "a", "horror", "to", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 449, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110816pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBG", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 450, "question": "So why is 2090 any worse than that?", "question_tokens": ["So", "why", "is", "2090", "any", "worse", "than", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WRB", "VBZ", "CD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 451, "answer": "I'm not horrified by any thought of dying, because I believe you go on to a celestial place which is wonderful.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "not", "horrified", "by", "any", "thought", "of", "dying", ",", "because", "I", "believe", "you", "go", "on", "to", "a", "celestial", "place", "which", "is", "wonderful", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["2090"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110816pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 453, "question": "Where is your evidence of a celestial place?", "question_tokens": ["Where", "is", "your", "evidence", "of", "a", "celestial", "place", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 454, "answer": "I come back to the issue of creation.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "come", "back", "to", "the", "issue", "of", "creation", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110816pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "DT", ",", "DT", ",", "RB", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 470, "question": "We're all a bit crazy, a bit nuts?", "question_tokens": ["We", "'re", "all", "a", "bit", "crazy", ",", "a", "bit", "nuts", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 471, "answer": "No, no, no, not at all.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "no", ",", "no", ",", "not", "at", "all", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110816pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBP", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 490, "question": "Yeah, Thor?", "question_tokens": ["Yeah", ",", "Thor", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 491, "answer": "No, because that is not the type of God I believe in.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "because", "that", "is", "not", "the", "type", "of", "God", "I", "believe", "in", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110816pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 496, "question": "Why?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 497, "answer": "Because it's not the same thing.", "answer_tokens": ["Because", "it", "'s", "not", "the", "same", "thing", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110816pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "CC", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 505, "question": "Even though there are different rules?", "question_tokens": ["Even", "though", "there", "are", "different", "rules", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "EX", "VBP", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 506, "answer": "No, but I have an absolute respect for anybody from any religion that has a spiritual and religious conviction and belief in a god-like entity in their lives.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "but", "I", "have", "an", "absolute", "respect", "for", "anybody", "from", "any", "religion", "that", "has", "a", "spiritual", "and", "religious", "conviction", "and", "belief", "in", "a", "god-like", "entity", "in", "their", "lives", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110816pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 519, "question": "What if you were dying, hypothetically?", "question_tokens": ["What", "if", "you", "were", "dying", ",", "hypothetically", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 520, "answer": "I am dying.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "am", "dying", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110816pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 527, "question": "Do you know this?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "know", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 528, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110816pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "EX", "VBZ", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "JJR", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 572, "question": "Why would you live in Las Vegas?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "would", "you", "live", "in", "Las", "Vegas", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 573, "answer": "Because there is nothing I like doing more than my show.", "answer_tokens": ["Because", "there", "is", "nothing", "I", "like", "doing", "more", "than", "my", "show", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Las Vegas"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110816pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "JJS", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 590, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 591, "answer": "At least I got a prayer.", "answer_tokens": ["At", "least", "I", "got", "a", "prayer", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110816pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "RBS", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 599, "question": "What's the answer?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "the", "answer", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 600, "answer": "I always seem to think that the most important thing is individuals.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "always", "seem", "to", "think", "that", "the", "most", "important", "thing", "is", "individuals", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110816pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 657, "question": "They do?", "question_tokens": ["They", "do", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 658, "answer": "I think so.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "so", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110816pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 661, "question": "On a mass scale?", "question_tokens": ["On", "a", "mass", "scale", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 662, "answer": "Yeah.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110816pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 663, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 664, "answer": "I think.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110816pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "RB", ",", "RB", "JJR", "."], "qSentId": 667, "question": "ORGAN: What is the one thing you would do, if you were president, to get Americans back to work?", "question_tokens": ["ORGAN", ":", "What", "is", "the", "one", "thing", "you", "would", "do", ",", "if", "you", "were", "president", ",", "to", "get", "Americans", "back", "to", "work", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "CD", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", ",", "TO", "VB", "NNPS", "RB", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 668, "answer": "What I would do is I think make the government much, much smaller.", "answer_tokens": ["What", "I", "would", "do", "is", "I", "think", "make", "the", "government", "much", ",", "much", "smaller", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110816pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 694, "question": "Moxie Crime Fighter?", "question_tokens": ["Moxie", "Crime", "Fighter", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 695, "answer": "Moxie.", "answer_tokens": ["Moxie", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110816pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 716, "question": "Is she old enough to realize what you've done?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "she", "old", "enough", "to", "realize", "what", "you", "'ve", "done", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "JJ", "RB", "TO", "VB", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 717, "answer": "Better than that.", "answer_tokens": ["Better", "than", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110816pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 737, "question": "Does it feel like a marriage to you?", "question_tokens": ["Does", "it", "feel", "like", "a", "marriage", "to", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 738, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110816pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 751, "question": "And how do you get on now?", "question_tokens": ["And", "how", "do", "you", "get", "on", "now", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 752, "answer": "ILLETTE: Wonderfully.", "answer_tokens": ["ILLETTE", ":", "Wonderfully", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110816pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 759, "question": "Do you socialize away from work?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "socialize", "away", "from", "work", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "RP", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 760, "answer": "About twice a year we go out socially together.", "answer_tokens": ["About", "twice", "a", "year", "we", "go", "out", "socially", "together", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110816pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "DT", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 763, "question": "Do you do all the talking?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "do", "all", "the", "talking", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PDT", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 764, "answer": "No, no, no.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "no", ",", "no", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110816pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJR", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 767, "question": "So he's perfectly garrulous when you have dinner?", "question_tokens": ["So", "he", "'s", "perfectly", "garrulous", "when", "you", "have", "dinner", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "JJR", "."], "aSentId": 768, "answer": "More so than me.", "answer_tokens": ["More", "so", "than", "me", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110816pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "JJR", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 775, "question": "If I could give you the power of prayer, I awarded it to you, what would you pray for?", "question_tokens": ["If", "I", "could", "give", "you", "the", "power", "of", "prayer", ",", "I", "awarded", "it", "to", "you", ",", "what", "would", "you", "pray", "for", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "TO", "PRP", ",", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 776, "answer": "I would pray, I think, for more perfect knowledge.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "would", "pray", ",", "I", "think", ",", "for", "more", "perfect", "knowledge", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110816pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 783, "question": "Why surprising?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "surprising", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 784, "answer": "I don't know.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]